迈克:我怎么会让你说服我,起这么早的床,
Mike: How the heck did I let you talk me into getting up before the pigs
只是为了买一张该死的演唱会门票?
just to get tickets to a stupid concert?
本:因为你答应了,一小时我会给你5块钱,
Ben: Because you are broke, and I'm paying you five bucks an hour.
希望轮到我们的时候还剩一些好票.
I hope we get there while there's still some good tickets left.
迈克:呵呵,好的.我口袋里又有一个五块了.
Mike: He he.Alright.That's another five bucks in my pocket.
本:我还能付得起.
Ben: And while I can still afford them.
迈克:这儿的所有人都是来看约纳森?基思的.天哪!
Mike: So all these people are here to see Jonathon Keith.Kids today!
本:这有问题吗?
Ben: What's wrong with him?
迈克:没有,但是依我看,他不如沃特埃沃.
Mike: Nothing, but let's face it, he's not The Whatever.
本:胡?
Ben: The who?
迈克:不,不是胡.
Mike: No, not The Who.That's that old band that dad like.
那是爸爸喜欢的老乐队.我是说沃特埃沃.太好了!
I'm talking about The Whatever.Count Vay.Alright!
(女孩插队)
(girl pushes in)
本:嘿!
Ben: Hey!
迈克:嘿!你在干什么……吃早餐吗?啊,你叫什么?
Mike: Hey!What the heck are you doing...for breakfast?Ah, what's your name?
埃莉:埃莉.
Ellie: Ellie.
本:嘿,和约纳森妻子的名字一样.
Ben: Hey, that's the same name as Jonathon's wife.
埃莉:我知道.你的名字呢?
Ellie: I know.What's your name?
迈克:约纳森.
Mike: Jonathon.
埃莉:喔!
Ellie: Wow!
迈克:是的,太巧了.
Mike: Yeah, what a coincidence, hu?
本:别听他的,他不是约纳森,他只是我的出租车司机.
Ben: Don't listen to him.His name's not Jonathon.He's just my taxi driver.
迈克:你说我?我是这儿的唯一一个出租车司机.
Mike: You talking to me?I'm the only taxi driver here.
你玩过电影吗?
Have you ever seen the movie "Taxi Driver"?
埃莉:丹尼 德维托演的路易斯.
Ellie: With Danny Devito as Louis.
迈克:不是,是罗伯特?
Mike: No, with Robert De Niro as an insane person.
德尼洛演一个疯子.看,他开始自言自语了,
See he starts to talk to himself.And makes no sense whatsoever.
总是很莫名其妙,就像我现在一样.
Kind of like I'm doing right now.
埃莉:嗯.
Ellie: Uh hu.
本:嘿,看!约纳森来了.
Ben: Hey look!Jonathon's on.
迈克:我是唯一一个没有听见音乐的人吗?
Mike: Am I the only one who doesn't hear any music?
本:美妙的歌曲?
Ben: Great song hu?
埃莉:你说了.
Ellie: You said it.
男人:嘿,你们相信吗?演唱会的票卖完了.
Man: Hey folks, can you believe it?The concert's sold out.
所有人:哦,不!
Everyone: Oh no!
男人:我都在这儿排队三天了.
Man: And I've been camped out here for three days man.
本:我不相信,我已经省了好几个月的钱.
Ben: I can't believe this.I've been saving my money for months.
我该怎么办?
What am I going to do?
迈克:嘿,看开点,
Mike: Hey, look on the bright side Bennie.
本.现在你又可以给你的出租司机多付点小费了.
Now you can pay your taxi driver that big tip that he deserves.
本:你说我?
Ben: You talking to me?
杰森:我说对了吧?只有你们两个在排队吧?
Jason: So was I right?You two were the only guys in line?
本:票已经卖光了.
Ben: It was sold out.
麦琪:哦,小南瓜.
Maggie: Oh pumpkin.
杰森:很抱歉,本.
Jason: Sorry Ben.
本:我说过,我们应该一大早就去排队.
Ben: Like I said, we should have camped out like I wanted.
迈克:如果我有闹钟,我可以早点起来.
Mike: If I'd have been on the clock, I could have been up for it.
开萝尔:迈克,有时候你的话不经过大脑.
Carol: Mike, sometimes you can be so thoughtless in what you say.
本:迈克!卖完,这是我听过的最残忍的一个词.
Ben: Man!Sold out, the cruelest word I ever heard.
开萝尔:本,那实际上是两个词.
Carol: Well actually Ben, it's two words.
本:开萝尔,我可以想起另两个词.
Ben: Carol, I can think of another two words.
麦琪:本!
Maggie: Ben!
本:对不起,我只是很难过.
Ben: Sorry.I'm just upset.
杰森:来,本.还有其他的演唱会.
Jason: Come on Ben.There'll be other concerts.
本:没有约纳森的.
Ben: Not Jonathon's.
杰森:我真希望能给你做些什么,儿子.
Jason: Well I wished there was something I could do son.
迈克:你可以找个票贩子,爸爸.
Mike: You could call a scalper dad.
我相信你花两百块钱肯定可以买到一张.
I'm sure the tickets would only be about two hundred bucks a piece.
杰森:就像我说的,我希望我能做些什么.
Jason: Like I said.I wish there was something I could do.
本:你们不知道谁会有票吗?
Ben: Don't you guys know anybody who might have tickets?
杰森:我认识的所有人都是精神病学家,本.
Jason: All I know are psychiatrists Ben.
本:我在一本歌迷杂志上看到,约纳森的爸爸是一名精神病学家.
Ben: Well I was reading in a fan magazine that Jonathon's dad is a psychiatrist.
杰森:是的,我不认识每一个精神病学家.
Jason: Yeah, well I don't know every psychiatrist.
本:亚历山大 基思医生呢?
Ben: Doctor Alexander Keith?
杰森:亚历山大 基思?
Jason: Alex Keith?
本:嗯.
Ben: Uh hu.
杰森:来自波士顿?
Jason: From Boston?
本:嗯.
Ben: Uh hu.
杰森:我认识他,来自美德学校,麦琪,你记得吗?
Jason: I know him.From med school Maggie.Do you remember?
麦琪:是的,是那个喜欢参加各种聚会的家伙吗?
Maggie: Well yes.Is he the guy that though all those parties?
本:太好了.
Ben: This is great.
麦琪:哦!
Maggie: Oh!
开萝尔:怎么了?
Carol: What's the matter?
麦琪:真希望我能嫁给这样一个老男人,有一个儿子是摇滚明星.
Maggie: I'm married to a man old enough to have a son as a rock star.
杰森:想想我的感受.
Jason: Think how I feel.
杰森:哈!亚历山大的电话号码就在这儿.
Jason: Ha!Alex's number is right here.
麦琪:你上次你和他说话是在什么时候?
Maggie: When was the last time you spoke to him?
杰森:上次同学聚会的时候.
Jason: At the last reunion.
麦琪:宝贝,已经很久了.
Maggie: Honey, that's quite a while ago.
杰森:哦,是的,不过你知道亚历山大是个什么样的人.
Jason: Oh yeah, but you remember the kind of guy Alex is.
你可以多年不和他联系,但只要你一见面,
You can go for years without talking to him,
他还会把你当成朋友.你好,亚历山大,
and the minute you do it's like not a day has passed.Hello Alex.Jason.
我是杰森 西维尔,医学院,科内尔.
Seaver.Medical School.Cornell.Right right.No, no.Full head of hair.
对的,对的,
Yeah, so how have you been?Great.
不,不是,我有头发.
Yeah look, I was wondering since you and I spoke at that last reunion
你好吗?太好了,自从上次和你在同学聚会上见面以来,
a couple of years ago and, uh, you said make sure you keep in touch...
已经好几年了,你说过希望我们保持联系……是的,你说了.
Yeah, you said that.
你知道吗,我儿子,
Well you know my son, he thinks that your son is just the most unbeliev...
他认为你儿子非常了不起……我真不知道有好多人找你要票.不,你有权利抱怨.
No I have no idea how many people hit you up for tickets.
不,不,那算了,
No, you have every right to resent that.No, no, that's it.
我随便问问.我们下次同学聚会再见面,
I just wanted to touch base.Yeah so I'll see you at the next reunion.
也许不会.好的,再见.
Or not.Yeah bye.
麦琪:你要了几张票?
Maggie: How many tickets did you get?
杰森:麦琪.
Jason: Maggie.
麦琪:哦,宝贝.我开个小玩笑,想让你振作起来.
Maggie: Oh honey, I'm just trying to cheer you up with a little joke.
杰森:本太想去看演唱会了,我现在就去找个票贩子,
Jason: Ben would have been so happy.
花上四百元.
Now I've got to go call a scalper and spend four hundred bucks.
麦琪:我有办法了.
Maggie: I've got an idea.
杰森:太好了.
Jason: I love it.
麦琪:我以前怎么没想到呢?
Maggie: I don't know why id didn't think of this before.
杰森:是什么?
Jason: What is it?
麦琪:我要打电话给电视台的娱乐编辑.是的,我是麦琪 马隆,我找一下史蒂夫 杰金斯.他总是吹牛说认识音乐界的所有人.
Maggie: I'm going to call the entertainment editor at the station.Yes this is Maggie Malone for Steve Jerkins.He's always bragging about his music contacts.
杰森:值得一试.
Jason: Yeah well it's worth a shot.
麦琪:你好,史蒂夫,
Maggie: Hello Steve.This is Maggie.I've got a question.
我是麦琪.我有件事,
See my son Ben is a big fan of Jonathon Keith,
我的儿子本是约纳森 基思的超级歌迷,他为了这些票简直想……
and he would just kill for tickets to...uh hu.
杰森:别难过,宝贝,我也失败过.
Jason: Don't feel bad sweetheart.I failed too.
麦琪:那真是太好了,
Maggie: That would be wonderful.
如果你和我今晚带本去怎么样?
Jason, how about if you and me take Ben tonight?
杰森:可以.
Jason: Sure.
麦琪:哦,史蒂夫,我非常谢谢你.哦,不,不,
Maggie: Oh Steve, I can't thank you enough.Oh no, no, no.
不,三张票足够了.哦,别说傻话了,你不用派个豪华轿车来.
Three tickets is plenty.Oh don't be silly.You don't have to send a limo.
本:喔!
Ben: Wow!
麦琪:是的,今天下午我们去场馆,
Maggie: Yes, and this afternoon we can go down to the arena and watch
看他们为今晚的演唱会调音.
them do the sound check for tonight's concert.
本:我去看约纳森怎么准备演出的?
Ben: I get to watch Jonathon set up for the show?
杰森:是的.
Jason: Uh hu.
迈克:你从你的老朋友那弄到票了,太好了,爸爸,我就知道我会从某个地方得到礼物的.
Mike: You conned your old pal into giving you the tickets.Alright dad.I knew I got my gift from some place.
本:谢谢你,爸爸.谢谢你,谢谢你.
Ben: Thank you dad.Thank you, thank you.
迈克:本,本,本.我想你该知道感激和崇拜之间的差异了.好了吗?
Mike: Ben Ben Bennie.I think its time you learned the difference between gratitude and groveling.Alright?
杰森:是的,本.
Jason: Yeah, easy Ben.The look on your face is thanks enough for me.
你脸上的表现说明你很感谢我.哦,
Oh, did I forget to mention that your mum actually got the tickets and
我忘了提到你妈妈了,是她弄到了票,安排了每一件事?
arranged everything?I meant to mention that.I just ...
我早就想说.我只是……我早应该提……
I might have mentioned it to...
迈克:哦.
Mike: Yeah.
麦琪:克莉丝在睡觉,她要吃的东西在冰箱里.
Maggie: Well Chrissy's napping and her food is in the refrigerator.
剧场的电话是……
The number to the Coliseum is...
开萝尔:喔,你为什么告诉我?
Carol: Wow wow, why are you telling me?
麦琪:因为你这个下午要看孩子.
Maggie: Because you are going to baby-sit this afternoon.
开萝尔:哦,妈妈,我想看,但是我对黛比说过我们要去看电影的.
Carol: Oh mum, I would but I told Debbie we would go to a movie.
麦琪:哦,宝贝,
Maggie: Oh honey.Your father and I are really stuck.
我和你爸爸真得没法分身.如果我给你十美元,怎么样?
What if I offered you ten dollars?
开萝尔:妈妈,我不指望看孩子有报酬,
Carol: Mum, I do not expect to get paid to baby-sit.It's my family duty.
那是我的家庭责任.但是我不能对黛比说话不算数啊.
But I just can't break a commitment to Debbie.
麦琪:20?
Maggie: Twenty?
开萝尔:黛比是谁?
Carol: Who's Debbie?
杰森:宝贝,迈克今天主动表示要看孩子.
Jason: Honey, mike has graciously agreed to baby-sit today.
麦琪:是吗,多少钱?
Maggie: Yeah, how much?
迈克:妈妈,我不要钱,那是我的家庭责任.
Mike: Mother, I do not expect to be paid to baby-sit.It's a family duty.
麦琪:杰森?
Maggie: Jason?
杰森:20元.
Jason: Twenty bucks.
麦琪:好,开萝尔,你和黛比去看电影吧.
Maggie: Ok Carol, you can got to the movies with Debbie.
开萝尔:但是,妈妈,我真的需要钱,你答应了.
Carol: But mum, I really need the money, and you promised.
杰森:迈克,今天放你走,现在你可以去参加聚会了.
Jason: Mike, this let's you off the hook.Now you can go to your party.
迈克:什么聚会?我是说,你什么意思,爸爸.我准备好今晚看孩子了,而且,我已经没钱了.
Mike: What party?I mean uh, what do you mean dad.I was all psyched to baby-sit tonight.Besides, 'm broke.
杰森:嘿,麦琪,
Jason: Hey Maggie.This is quite a bargain.
这是一个好买卖,两人看孩子,一人五块钱.
Two babysitters for the price of five.
本:约纳森的化妆间肯定是在这儿.
Ben: Jonathon's dressing room has got to be around here somewhere.
麦琪:杰森,声音特别吵,
Maggie: Jason, was that sound check especially loud,
我是不是比我想得要老啊,已经不适应了.
or am I getting older than I thought?
杰森:老了.
Jason: Older.
麦琪:老了.
Maggie: Older.
杰森:你的听力很好,说明你还是一个年轻女郎.
Jason: See, your hearing is fine.You're a young woman.
本:就是那个门,我打赌,肯定是.
Ben: That's the door.I bet you that's it.
杰森:本,门上写着"管理员".
Jason: Ben, that door says janitor.
本:这可能只是用来骗傻瓜的.但是这骗不了我.
Ben: That's probably just to fool the bozoz.But it didn't fool me.
杰森:你知道,他可能回到宾馆里了,
Jason: Well you know, he may have gone back to his hotel or something.
他甚至可能不在这,猫王埃尔维斯就经常这样.
He may not even be around here.That's the way Elvis used to do it.
本:爸爸,埃尔维斯死了.
Ben: Dad, Elvis is dead.
男人甲:好了,约纳森想尽快要一些热咖啡送到化妆间.
Man: Alright, Jonathon wants some hot coffee in his dressing room ASAP.
男人乙:现在是下午三点,我去哪儿找热咖啡呢?好吧,我去.
Man 2: Where am I going to find hot coffee at three o'clock in the afternoon?Ok, I'm on it.
本:他在这儿,约纳森在这儿!我又要去厕所了.
Ben: He's here.Jonathon's here!I got to got o the bathroom again.
麦琪:那不是一个坏主意.
Maggie: That's not a bad idea.
杰森:什么,你也太激动了?
Jason: What, the excitement is too much for you too?
麦琪:什么?
Maggie: What?
杰森:去厕所.
Jason: Just go to the bathroom.
麦琪:谢谢你,谢谢你.
Maggie: Thank you, thank you.
杰森:哦,对不起,我没看见你.
Jason: Oh sorry.I didn't see you.
男人丙:没关系.
Man 3: No sweat pops.
杰森:流行乐!哈哈哈.你一说话我就看出来了.哦,对不起,约纳森,约纳森,我可以得到你的亲笔签名吗?
Jason: Pops!Ha ha ha.You know they say the eyes are the first to go.Oh uh.Excuse me Jonathon, Jonathon.Could I get your autograph?
约纳森:哦,好,没问题.你知道,很高兴能有你这么大年纪的歌迷.
Jonathon: Oh yeah.No problem man.You know it's nice to have fans your age.
杰森:我不是你的歌迷,我儿子是你的超级歌迷,
Jason: I'm not a fan of yours.My son is a big fan of yours.
他叫本.你能写上本的名字吗?我认识你的父亲.
His name's Ben.Could you make it out to Ben?I knew you dad, you know.
约纳森:是的,我也是.
Jonathon: Yeah, me too.
杰森:医学院,科内尔,
Jason: Medical school.Cornell.
他对你说过尸体失踪的事吗?
Did he ever tell you the story of the missing Cadaver?
约纳森:不,他没有.
Jonathon: No.No he didn't.
杰森:我想我最好也不告诉你,哦,谢谢,我是杰森 西维尔.
Jason: I guess I better not tell you either hu.Oh thanks.I'm Jason Seaver.
约纳森:约纳森 基思.
Jonathon: Jonathon Keith.
杰森:我知道,
Jason: I know.Oh boy, my son's going to die you know.
我儿子特别迷恋你.
He's had us out here for the last hour,
他让我们一直在这儿等,只是想看看你,
just to try to get a glimpse of you,
他刚因为要去小便而走开.
and his kidneys pick now to pull him away.
男人乙:你好,约纳森,咖啡十分钟后来.
Man 2: Yo Jonathon.That coffee will be here in about ten minutes.
约纳森:好的,谢谢你.见到你很高兴,我要走了.
Jonathon: Alright.Thanks pal.Well it's been a pleasure.Got to run.
杰森:嘿嘿,喔喔,哈哈,呃呃,约纳森.不好意思,我知道你特别的忙,今天要开演唱会,但是我儿子马上就过来,我保证,如果你能够等上一点点,一点点的时间,你会看见……
Jason: Hey hey.wo wo.Ha ha.Uh uh Jonathon.Pardon me I know you got a million things to do, it being concert day and everything, but he'll be down here in about any second, I swear, so if you could just wait just a tinsy tinsy minute, you'll see...
约纳森:好的,好的.我对你说,如果他能在十分钟内回来,就带他到我的化妆间来,我很乐意见他.
Jonathon: Alright, alright, I'll tell you what man.If he's back within ten minutes, spring him by my dressing room.I'd be more than happy to say hello.
杰森:哦,这真是太好了.
Jason: Oh, that would be so terrific.
约纳森:我房间门上有一个看门人的标记,偏偏傻瓜的.
Jonathon.Mine's the one marked janitor.Helps keep the bozos away.
杰森:骗不了我.
Jason: Didn't fool me.
约纳森:我们回头见.
Jonathon: So, uh, I'll see you round.
杰森:回头见.
Jason: See you.
约纳森:好的!
Jonathon: Alright!
杰森:好的.哈,哈,哈,好的.哦,好人.
Jason: Alright.Ha ha ha.Alright.Oh, nice guy.
约纳森:托尼,你去哪了?
Jonathon: Tony, where you been man?
如果我有错了你得纠正我,但是保护我也是你的责任,对吧?
Correct me if I'm wrong, but is it not your job to protect me?
男人甲:我去拿个油炸圈饼.
Man 1: I was getting a doughnut.
约纳森:你出去填饱肚子的时候,有个混蛋缠住我,
Jonathon: You're out stuffing your fat face man,
要我见他那该死的儿子.
and some bozo hits on me to meet his stupid kid.
男人甲:我很抱歉.
Man 1: I'm sorry.
约纳森:哦,你很抱歉,
Jonathon: Oh, you're sorry.Well sorry is not good enough.
抱歉有什么用.现在我要见这家伙的臭小子.为什么?
Now I will meet this guy's brat.Why?Because I'm a nice guy.
因为我是一个好人,所以你去把摄影师找来,拍一些照片作宣传.
So go get this pain in the butt photographer and let's get some PR mileage
不过,你得保证以后不能让那些混蛋见我.
out of this.Please.And make sure that future bozos stay out of my face.
男人甲:嘿!
Man 1: Hey!
杰森:好了,我在这儿.我就是那个混蛋,麦琪.
Jason: It's alright, I belong here.I'm the original bozo.Maggie.
麦琪:本在哪儿?
Maggie: Where's Ben?
杰森:还在厕所里.
Jason: Still in the bathroom.
麦琪:他们还说女人离不开厕所呢.
Maggie: And they say women take forever.
杰森:嘿,我刚才见了约纳森 基思,我……
Jason: hey I just met Jonathon Keith, and I...
麦琪:哦,他还签了名.
Maggie: Oh and he signed it.
杰森:是的,
Jason: Yeah, well I was just standing here and he came over,
他走过来时我刚才恰好站在这,我们开始交谈,
we started talking and before I knew it he said Ben could meet him in
他说本可以去他的化妆间见他.
the dressing room.
麦琪:你在开玩笑?
Maggie: Are you kidding?
杰森:哦,但是我告诉你,我听见他说……
Jason: Yeah, but I got to tell you, I heard him say...
麦琪:本,本,
Maggie: Ben.Ben, your father has wonderful news.
你爸爸有好消息.
He's arranged it so that you can go back to Jonathon's dressing room and
他安排好了,你可以去约纳森的化妆间见他.
meet him.
本:喔!
Ben: Wow!
杰森:是的,本,就一分钟.在你之前……本.很高兴再次见到你.
Jason: Yeah Ben, just a minute.Before you do...Ben.Nice to see you again.
摄影师:我来拍下来.
Photographer: Make me believe it.
本:好的,我的名字是……嗯……嗯,嗯.
Ben: Ok, so where was I.Ok, yeah, my names...um...Um, um
杰森:本 西维尔.
Jason: Ben Seaver.
本:是的.
Ben: Yeah.
杰森:约纳森,这是我的妻子麦琪,她也见过你的爸爸.
Jason: And Jonathon, this is my wife Maggie.She's also met your dad.
约纳森:非常非常高兴见到你们.
Jonathon: It's very very nice to meet you.
麦琪:我很荣幸.
Maggie: My pleasure.
约纳森:这是我的经纪人托尼,有时候他照顾我.
Jonathon: And this is my road manager Tony.He takes care of me.Sometimes.
杰森:我听说了.
Jason: I've heard.
摄影师:嘿,约纳森,你的手搂着他怎么样,我来拍.
Photographer: Hey Jonathon, how about one with your arm around him.Make me believe it.
麦琪:我敢说本是你最忠实的歌迷,他知道你的所有的事.
Maggie: I bet Ben is your biggest fan.He knows everything about you.
约纳森:哦,我真希望这样.哈哈.
Jonathon: Oh well I hope not.Ha ha.
杰森:哈,哈,哈.
Jason: Ha ha ha.
本:我知道你24岁,来自波士顿,我知道你的歌曲"我的唯一"是写给你的妻子埃莉.
Ben: Well, I know you are twenty four, you're from Boston.I know that your song "My only one" was written for your wife Ellie.
约纳森:她就是我的唯一,她和孩子在家呢.
Jonathon: Well she is my only one.She's at home with the baby.
麦琪:啊!
Maggie: Ah!
本:我知道"不要灰心"的完整歌词.不要灰心,呃,呃,
Ben: I know all the words to "Don't be Down".
不要灰心,呃,呃,不要……
Don't be down, uh hu, uh hu.Don't be down, uh hu, uh hu.Don't be...
约纳森:很好.
Jonathon: Great.
摄影师:约纳森,拍一张你们交谈时的照片.
Photographer: Ah Jonathon, one where you are interested in what he's saying.
约纳森:你们怎么跑到后台来的?
Jonathon: So how did you end up crashing back stage?
摄影师:我拍了.
Photographer: Make me believe it.
本:我妈妈打电话给她电视台的同事.
Ben: My mum called this guy at her TV station.
麦琪:看,我自己也是一个明星,
Maggie: See, I'm kind of a celebrity myself.
我是19频道的记者.
I'm a reporter for Channel Nineteen.
约纳森:哦,是的,很棒.
Jonathon: Oh yeah.Very cool.
麦琪:我想你认识我们的编辑,史蒂夫 杰金斯?
Maggie: I think you know our editor.Steve Jerkins?
约纳森:是的,是的,我认识.
Jonathon: Yeah.Yes, I do.
麦琪:他给了我们票.
Maggie: He got us press seats.
摄影师:我拍好了,谢谢.
Photographer: I got what I need.Thanks.
约纳森:很好,很高兴见到你.
Jonathon: well, it's been nice meeting you.
本:你有只叫格莱美的狗,是吗?
Ben: Is it true you've got a dog named Grammy?
约纳森:是的……
Jonathon: Yeah...
本:那是你的最心爱的吉他吗?
Ben: Is that your favorite guitar?
约纳森:好的,托尼,你给我们的客人弄几张今晚演出前排的票吧.
Jonathon: Ok Tony, would you make sure our guests receive front row tickets for tonight's show?
男人甲:嗯.
Man 1: Uh hu.
本:前排!
Ben: Front row!
约纳森:嘿,我有办法.
Jonathon: Hey, I got connections.
本:谢谢,约纳森.
Ben: Thanks Jonathon.
麦琪:谢谢你.
Maggie: Thank you.
约纳森:好的,再见.希望你们喜欢这次演出.
Jonathon: Alright.Bye.You folks enjoy the show.
本:再见.
Ben: Bye.
约纳森:再见.
Jonathon: Bye bye.
男人乙:约纳森,咖啡来了.
Man 2: Jonathon, Coffee's here.
约纳森:来杯瓦尔迪兹咖啡真不错.
Jonathon: One Valdez would approve.
本:他喜欢我,他真的喜欢我,一个了不起的人.
Ben: He liked me.He really liked me.What a great guy.
杰森:他真的喜欢了不起的人.
Jason: He sure seems like a great guy.
本:是的,我真想马上让维托,斯汀奇和贝博斯这些哥们看到我的相片,哦,不!我忘了我的相片,我马上回来.
Ben: Yeah, I can't wait to show my album to Veto and Stinky and the Bebos brothers.Oh no!I forgot my album.I'll be right back.
麦琪:杰森,等一下,
Maggie: Jason, after a while, didn't you get the sense that Jonathon was,
你不觉得约纳森,唉,我不清楚……
uh, I don't know...
杰森:很彪悍?他的父亲也是.
Jason: Full of bull?So was his father.
本:对不起,约纳森,我忘了我的……
Ben: Sorry Jonathon, I forgot my...
约纳森:该死的,我很忙.
Jonathon: Damn it.I'm busy.
本:那不是埃莉.
Ben: That's not Ellie.
约纳森:你赶紧离开这儿,你这个鼻子黑黑的臭小子!出去!
Jonathon: Would you get the hell out of here.You snot nosed brat!Get out!
出去!出去!出去!
Out !Out!Get out.
麦琪:他叫你混蛋?
Maggie: He called you a bozo?
杰森:是的.
Jason: Uh hu.
麦琪:但是他甚至不认识你.我是说……
Maggie: But he doesn't even know you.I mean...
杰森:我知道你的意思.
Jason: I know what you mean.
麦琪:他来了.小南瓜,你准备好了吗?
Maggie: Oh here he comes.Pumpkin, are you ready to go?
本:嗯.
Ben: Uh hu.
杰森:你拿回你的相片了吗?
Jason: You got your album?
本:嗯.
Ben: Uh hu.
杰森:你见了约纳森?
Jason: You got to see Jonathon?
本:我见了.
Ben: I sure did.
杰森:好的.
Jason: Ok.
开萝尔:迈克,克莉丝要换衣服了.
Carol: Mike, Chrissy needs to be changed.
迈克:不,她不用.
Mike: No she doesn't.
开萝尔:那你来.
Carol: Then you do.
迈克:好了,好了,她要.我们找个公平又公正的办法决定谁来给克莉丝换衣服,,好,我们投币.正面,你看.
Mike: Alright, alright.She does.Well decide who changes Chrissy, fair and square.Alright, we'll
flip for it.Heads.You look
开萝尔:正面!我们走,克莉丝.
Carol: Heads!Let's go.Chrissy.
迈克:开萝尔,两个人看孩子还真是有好处.你知道他们说什么?人多力量大,尤其是在投币的时候.嘿嘿,你们好.
Mike: You know, it's a good thing we're both babysitting tonight Carol.You know what they say?Two heads are always better than one.Especially on coins.Hey hey guys.
杰森:嘿,迈克.
Jason: Hey Mike.
迈克:音效怎样?
Mike: How was that sound check?
麦琪:太吵了,但是很兴奋.
Maggie: Loud, but it was exciting.
杰森:非常兴奋.阿司匹林在哪?
Jason: Very.Where are the aspirin?
本:我上楼去了.
Ben: I'm going upstairs.
杰森:好的,你想上楼打电话给你的朋友,告诉他们吗?
Jason: Yeah, you're going to go up and call your friends and tell them?
本:是的,那是一个好主意.
Ben: Yeah, that's a good idea.
迈克:对他们说什么?
Mike: Tell them what?
麦琪:本见了约纳森 基思.
Maggie: Ben got to meet Jonathon Keith.
迈克:嘿嘿!很好啊,本!他是你想的那样吗?
Mike: Hey hey!Alright Bennie!So was he everything you hoped he'd be?
本:更好.
Ben: More.
开萝尔:为什么我的所有硬币都不见了?
Carol: Why do I lose every single coin flip?
本:在这儿呢?
Ben: This belongs right here.
杰森:来,本.我们会很晚回来,
Jason: Come on Ben.We're going to be late.
开萝尔,我们11点回来,行吗?
Carol, we'll be back from the concert by eleven.Ok?
开萝尔:好的.
Carol: Ok.
男人:嘿,是这家吗?
Man: Hey, is this the right house?
杰森:是我家,有什么事吗?
Jason: It is for us.Can I help you?
男人:我是布姆 布姆.
Man: Yeah, I'm Boom Boom.
杰森:你来这儿接开萝尔吗?
Jason: You're not here to pick up Carol are you?
男人:不,我来这儿取票的.
Man: No, I'm here to pick up tickets.
杰森:什么票?
Jason: What tickets?
男人:约纳森 基思的演唱会票,前排,
Man: For the Jonathon Keith concert.Front row.
我知道这太让我高兴了,不过,嘿,
I know this is going to put me into hoc, but hey,
我们以前都没有去过,是吧?
who among us hasn't been there before?Right?
杰森:嘿,听着……
Jason: Hey listen...
男人:布姆 布姆
Man: Boom Boom.
杰森:布姆 布姆.是的,我不知道这事.
Jason: Boom Boom.Yeah.I don't know anything about this.
男人:哦,
Man: Oh, well I talked to a guy named Mike on the phone and he said
我是和一个叫迈克的小伙在电话里说的,
it's a done deal.
他说成交.他让我从后台进,
He said just to go to the back house and be sure not to disturb his
千万别打扰他的父母.
parents.
杰森:啊哈,看,布姆 布姆.我不想打断你,但这些票是不卖的.
Jason: Ah ha.Look Boom Boom, I don't want to break the news to you, but these tickets aren't for sale.
男人:很抱歉打扰你们,你是开萝尔吗?
Man: Oh, well sorry to disturb you then.Are you Carol?
开萝尔:不是.
Carol: No.
杰森:她不是.本!
Jason: No she's not.Ben!
本:在.
Ben: Yeah.
杰森:一个叫布姆 布姆的家伙刚走了,他说……本?
Jason: A guy named Boom Boom just left here and he said...Ben?
本:我感觉不舒服.
Ben: I don't feel too good.
杰森:哦,怎么了?
Jason: Oh, what's the matter?
本:我发热了.
Ben: I've got a fever.
杰森:128度.
Jason: A hundred and twenty eight.
本:因此我应当今晚待在家里,是吧?
Ben: So I should probably stay in tonight, hu?
杰森:是的,你也真是讨骂.
Jason: Yeah, and you should be basted too.
本:我知道很不好.
Ben: I knew it was bad.
杰森:怎么办呢,本?
Jason: What's going on Ben?
本:我对你说,我不是一个好人.
Ben: I told you.I'm not a well man.
杰森:你是用电灯泡烤的吧?
Jason: You held this up to the light bulb, didn't you?
本:是的,也许我没有发热,但是我仍然觉得恶心.
Ben: Ok, so maybe I don't have a temperature, but I'm still sick.
杰森:嗯.迈克为什么要卖你的票?
Jason: Uh hu.And what's this about Mike selling your tickets?
本:因为我不能去演唱会,
Ben: Well since I wasn't going to the concert,
我打算赚点小钱.
I figured I could make some easy money.
杰森:你那儿以前有一张约纳森 基思的海报吧?
Jason: You used to have a poster of Jonathon Keith up there, didn't you?
本:我取下来了.
Ben: I took it down.
杰森:为什么?
Jason: Why?
本:这让我恶心,像吃了只苍蝇.
Ben: It was making me sick.The ink or something.
杰森:你去后台取照片时发生了肯定发生了什么,是吧?
Jason: Something happened today when you went backstage to get your album,
嘿?记得吗?
didn't it?Uh?Hey?It's me remember.
本:爸爸,约纳森是个小人,
Ben: Dad, Jonathon is a real jerk.
我看见他在亲一个女孩,
I saw him kissing this lady who wasn't his wife and he called me a snot
那不是他的妻子,他叫我鼻子黑黑的臭小子.
nosed little brat.
杰森:很抱歉,本.
Jason: Sorry Ben.Hey I had a feeling that maybe Jonathon wasn't what you
嘿,我早感觉也许约纳森真的不是你想象的样子……
exactly what you thought when you...
本:他真虚伪,我讨厌他.
Ben: He's just a big phony.I hate him.I wish I hadn't seen him today.
我真希望今天没有见到他,
I don't want to see him or his stupid music again.
我不想再次看他和他那该死的音乐,我马上去扔了他的所有唱片.
I'm going to get rid of his records right now.
杰森:嘿,嘿,嘿!
Jason: Hey hey hey!
本:哦.不.
Ben: Oh no.
杰森:什么?
Jason: What?
本:如果我喜欢的那些人都像约纳森一样怎么办?
Ben: What if all the guys whose records I like are jerks like Jonathon?
如果所有名人都是这样?
What if all famous people are scum buckets?
杰森:嘿,冷静点.
Jason: Hey, calm down.Wait a second.Hey Ben.Now just a second.
等一下,嘿,本,
Now I don't know every famous person, but I'll tell you one thing,
只要一会.我不认识每一个名人,
I imagine they are just like everybody else.
但是我告诉你件事,我能想象他们和其他人也一样.有些人好,
Some are going to be nice and some aren't so nice.
有些人不好.你不能因为一个人就讨厌所有的人.
You can't hate everybody just because of one person.
本:我以为约纳森喜欢我,我以为我喜欢他.
Ben: I thought Jonathon liked me.I thought I liked him.
杰森:是的,但是你甚至不认识他,本.你所知道的不过是听过他的唱片,电视里听过他的讲话.你了解他吗?
Jason: Yeah, but you didn't even know him Ben.Come on, all you know about him is what you hear on his records and what he says on TV.What you read about him.
本:所以?
Ben: So?
杰森:所以我们人们不会总是你想象的那样.拿你妈妈来说,
Jason: So well the image isn't always what the person is like.
人们在电视里看她,
Now take your mum for instance.
觉得她很棒,理性,
People watch heron TV, they think she's this cool, rational,
可以做各种类型新闻的女人.
all business type news woman.And I know that's not the truth.
我知道这不是真的,不全都是事实.
That's not the whole truth.
本:爸爸,约纳森怎么能这样?
Ben: Man, how can Jonathon act like that?
我是说我不知道他的笑是什么样的?
I mean doesn't he know what a slime he is?
杰森:也许不是,也许不是.也许你比他更了解他.
Jason: Maybe not.Maybe not.Maybe you know him better than he knows himself.
本:这不会让我感觉更好.
Ben: That doesn't make me feel any better.
杰森:嘿,你还记得你第一次听说科米特不是一支真正青蛙的事吗?
Jason: Hey remember when you first heard that Kermit wasn't a real frog?
本:我记得.
Ben: Don't remind me.
杰森:好,几个月以后你才再次去看,
Jason: Yeah, well it took you months before you could even watch Sesame
但是你做到了.
Street again.But you did.
本:我忍不住,那很好看.
Ben: I couldn't help it.It's a good show.
杰森:好了,因此你不能因为发现了约纳森 基思的真相,就不喜欢他的音乐.
Jason: Ok, so just because you found out the truth about Jonathon Keith,
来吧,你很喜欢的那首歌怎么唱来着?不要灰心,
doesn't mean you can't enjoy his music.Come on.
呃,呃,
What's that song you like so much?Don't be down...hu hu.
不要灰心,呃,呃.
Don't be down, uh hu.
本:这男人还真的写了首好歌.
Ben: The man sure does write a good song.
杰森:好了.所以,
Jason: Yeah.So come-on,
来吧,
why don't you and I just go to that concert and see if we can have
我们应该去听演唱会,看看我们是否会玩得开心?
some fun?
本:我不能决定.
Ben: I don't know.
杰森:好了,如果你不想看见约纳森 基思,加里 普科茨就在镇上,我知道他是一个真正的好人.
Jason: Alright, if you don't want to see Jonathon Keith, Gary Puckets in town.Now I happen to know he's a real nice guy.
本:爸爸,我不喜欢加里 普科茨的音乐.
Ben: Dad, I don't like Gary Puckets' music.
杰森:哦,那么你去摇滚演唱会吗?
Jason: Oh, so you go to a rock concert for the music?
迈克:嘿,本,本,我有好消息.我找了一个家伙,他愿意花大价钱买我们的票.
Mike: Hey Bennie, Bennie, I have some great news.I have this guy who's coming
over who's willing to pay big bucks for those tickets
杰森:他的名字不是布姆 布姆吧?
Jason: His name wouldn't be Boom Boom, would it?
迈克:是的,是的,你认识他?
Mike: Yeah.Yeah, you know him?
杰森:我们一起上的美德学校.
Jason: We went to med school together.
迈克:好的,不管怎样,本这家伙……
Mike: Yeah, anyway, Bennie this guy is...
本:迈克,我不想卖掉它们.我们去演唱会,对吧,爸爸?
Ben: Mike, I don't want to sell them.We're going to the concert.Right dad?
杰森:对的.
Jason: Right.
本:你愿意放弃一张票三百元吗?
Ben: You are willing to give up three hundred bucks a ticket?
本:我们不在乎钱,是吧?
杰森:是的.
00:21:48,200
Ben: We don't care about the money, do we dad? Jason: No.